[speaker_0] So I want you to imagine for a moment that
[speaker_0] you are a catalog manager, for example, for an e-commerce
[speaker_0] company, and maybe you have a singular image of a
[speaker_0] model wearing a piece of clothing. But you don't have
[speaker_0] other angles of that image and you wanna use AI
[speaker_0] to generate those images. Well, check this out. As you
[speaker_0] can see, I wanna create a side view of this
[speaker_0] original photo that I have. Boom, I have a side
[speaker_0] view shot of that piece of clothing. Next, how about
[speaker_0] create a rear view of this photo? Boom, rear view
[speaker_0] of photo. Piece of cake. Check it out. This is
[speaker_1] Rossy Bytes. So what I wanna talk about today is
[speaker_0] in the Google AI Studio, the Gemini 2 Flash experimental
[speaker_0] model. So when you come into the AI Studio, and
[speaker_0] I'll include the link in the description below, you're gonna
[speaker_0] wanna come underneath Preview and select Gemini 2.0 Flash experimental.
[speaker_0] And then for output format, you wanna select images and
[speaker_0] text. So let's try out a few different examples of
[speaker_0] things that we can do with this. So to start,
[speaker_0] I'm gonna bring over an image that I already have
[speaker_0] of a model wearing a dress, and I'm gonna say
[speaker_0] create a side view of this photo. We'll just click
[speaker_0] Run. You can see how long it's taking for the
[speaker_0] Gemini to actually process this. So 4.8 seconds and it
[speaker_0] generated a pretty perfect side view of that particular clothing.
[speaker_0] So now let's do create a rear view of the
[speaker_0] same image. Go ahead and click Run. Again, five seconds
[speaker_0] or so, and we have a perfect rear image. If
[speaker_0] we open it up, it looks like the same model,
[speaker_0] same clothing. Okay, so next I'm gonna drag over a
[speaker_0] male model wearing a suit and I'm going to do
[speaker_0] the same test. I'm going to say create a side
[speaker_0] view of this photo, and we'll click Run. This one's
[speaker_0] taking a little longer, but boom, look at that. We
[speaker_0] have a side view shot of that guy wearing the
[speaker_0] suit. So just like we did with the model, I'll
[speaker_0] also come in and say create a rear view of
[speaker_0] the same photo and click Run. And there we have
[speaker_0] a rear view of the model wearing that suit. Okay,
[speaker_0] next I have this image of people playing in a
[speaker_0] yard on a patio at a house, and what I
[speaker_0] wanna do is I want to use this image and
[speaker_0] I want to try to remove the people out of
[speaker_0] the background. So I'm gonna say remove the people from
[speaker_0] this photo, and click Run. And within about nine seconds,
[speaker_0] take a look at that. All the people are gone
[speaker_0] from the photo. Generate a recipe with steps and images
[speaker_0] with each step of the way on how to make
[speaker_0] French toast. As we can see, we have ingredients and
[speaker_0] equipment. Crack the large eggs, add the milk, whisk the
[speaker_0] ingredients thoroughly, soak the bread. It's showing you the skillet
[speaker_0] with butter, cooking the French toast. That is insane. Then
[speaker_0] flipping it over. Repeat and add more butter. There you
[speaker_0] have your finished French toast, and then you can add
[speaker_0] some toppings. For this one I wanna say generate an
[speaker_0] intricate mandala coloring page in black and white. So kind
[speaker_0] of like just a coloring page in a coloring book.
[speaker_0] So that took about 15 seconds, but as you can
[speaker_0] see, we have a very intricate mandala drawing picture. So
[speaker_0] now I'm going to say now color this image in
[speaker_0] with vibrant and beautiful colors. Click Run. So that took
[speaker_0] about 20 seconds, but as we can see, we have
[speaker_0] a colored-in version of our mandala coloring page. So next
[speaker_0] I wanna see how Gemini does creating an image. So
[speaker_0] I'm basically asking with a very detailed prompt to create
[speaker_0] a black and white photograph of an elderly couple walking
[speaker_0] hand in hand in a park, and as you can
[speaker_0] see, it created a fantastic-looking image. So now I wanna
[speaker_0] have it color this picture in, so I'm gonna say
[speaker_0] colorize this image now. And within 5.2 seconds, look at
[speaker_0] that. We have a full-color version of the same photo.
[speaker_0] Next I'm gonna say add a small dog somewhere on
[speaker_0] the sidewalk. And look at that. Not only is it
[speaker_0] on the sidewalk, but the couple's actually walking it. Okay,
[speaker_0] so next I have an image of a sofa and
[speaker_0] I wanna try to change the color of the sofa
[speaker_0] so we could maybe have multiple variations of it. So
[speaker_0] I'm gonna say make this sofa blue colored, and then
[speaker_0] I'm gonna click Run. In about five seconds, look at
[speaker_0] that. We have a blue version of our sofa. So
[speaker_0] next I'm gonna say now make it burnt orange. And
[speaker_0] there's a burnt orange version of our sofa. I'm going
[speaker_0] to now say add a stylistic clock on the wall
[speaker_0] in the background. That's crazy. So now we have our
[speaker_0] stylistic clock on the wall in the background. So as
[speaker_0] you can see, this technology is absolutely amazing, and the
[speaker_0] really crazy thing about it is what I've shown you
[speaker_0] here is the worst it'll ever be. It's only going
[speaker_0] to get exponentially better. Let me know what you think
[speaker_0] of this in the comments, and if you'd like me
[speaker_0] to continue producing content like this, please click Like and
[speaker_0] Subscribe. Thank you and have a great day.